Lizpencer Adhiambo Okello

Telephone no: +254 715027595 Email: <u>lizpenseradhiambo@gmail.com</u>

DOB: 17th/10/1997

Personal Profile

Confident and skilled professional with over 4 years of diverse experience. I have excellent knowledge of community development and Nation building through the National Youth Service. I am experienced office assistant handling confidential paperwork and making routine office tasks as efficient as possible. I have strong multitasking organizational and data entry skills. I desire to obtain a meaningful and challenging position that will enable me to learn and gain more practical knowledge and skills for the benefit of the organization and me.

Education	
2019 - 2021	Accounting Technician Diploma Level 1 Jeremiah Nyaga Technical Institute
2017-2018	Paramilitary Training National Youth Service
2012- 2015	Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education Nyamasare Girls Secondary School

Certifications And Professional Qualifications

- 2016: Certificate in Case Microsoft skills.
- 2022: Certificate in Biomedical and Human research ;KEMRI
- Certificate of good clinical practice. NIDA clinical trial Network.

Skills

- Computer and Typing skills: proficient in Microsoft office and data entry
- Communication Skills: I am an empathic listener and persuasive speaker. Excellent oral communication and writing skills, interpersonal skills, and the ability to work in a team setting.
- Interpersonal and Teamwork Skills: I have the ability to work in a team, demonstrated the ability to build agreement, and navigate complex and appropriate frameworks.
- Analytical and Problem Solving: I have the ability to visualize, solve complicated problems in the best way I can, and make accurate and informed decisions.
- **Organization and Planning:** Detail oriented with strong organizational skills with the ability to prioritize and work effectively on multiple tasks in a demanding environment.
- **Flexibility:** Capacity to fit into most environments, maintain calm under pressure, and can adapt well to changes in the workplace.
- **Time Management Skills:** Excellent time management and organizational skills, and ability to handle multiple concurrent tasks and projects with minimal supervision.

Work Experience

September 2022- October 2022 Kenya Medical Research Institute and Liverpool school of Tropical Medicine

Position: Community Interviewer and Researcher on Malaria and Mosquito

Key Achievements:

successfully conducted Community interviews and emerged as the best team during the research process.

Responsibilities:

- Identify, recruit and administer informed consent to eligible participants
- Schedule and conduct in-depth interviews and focus group discussions with study participants – community members.
- Key in collected data.

Jan – August 2022

Tausi Hotel

Position:

- Ensuring financial transactions are properly recorded and accurately entered into the accounting systems.
- .Prepares monthly reports.
- . Monitors compliance with generally accepted accounting principles.

October 2019- December 2019 Ministry of Interior and Cordination

Position: Data entry Clerk

Responsibilities:

- Verification of birth and death certificates
- Keying in death and birth certificate detailed information for the government digitization program.

January 2016 – October 2017 Action Aid Kenya Nyarongi LRP

Position: Office Assistant

Responsibilities:

- Handling incoming calls and other communications.
- Managing filing system.
- Recording information as needed.
- Greeting clients and visitors as needed.
- Updating paperwork, maintaining documents, and word processing.
- Helping organize and maintain office common areas

Other Positions Held

- 2018- 2019: Office Assistant Nation building programme; National Youth Service
- August 2022: Polling Clerk; IEBC

Additional Information

Hobbies and Interests

Traveling, Community Work, Socializing

Referees

Hannington Kabaka

Former Community Development Facilitator; Action Aid Kenya Telephone no: +254 787810988

Email: hanningtonkabaka@gmail.com

Maurine Achieng Accountant; Hotel Tausi

Telephone no: +254 719250639 Email: staceymaurak@gmail.com

Oliver Towett

I.T Manager; Kenya Medical research institute

Telephone no: +254 702 921182